aspforums.net 2014-11-21

# Privacy Policy

__Privacy Policy[ __Ask Question](http://www.aspforums.net/Login/?NewQuestion=1&RedirectUrl=http%3a%2f%2fwww.aspforums.net%2fPrivacyPolicy%2f) [ ](http://www.aspforums.net/Login/?NewQuestion=1&RedirectUrl=http%3a%2f%2fwww.aspforums.net%2fPrivacyPolicy%2f)

* * *

ASPForums.Net makes sure that the privacy of all its registered users is secured. Whatever information gathered to identify the user to get its personal information and location is stored under the following security guidelines. The Privacy Policy of this website will be updated from time to time and hence please read this page in order to keep you updated with the changes. 

What information collected?

We collect your name, e-mail address and IP-address during signup. 

Why do we collect this information?

Your personal and contact details are used to identify you and contact you by sending alerts whenever some activity is performed on the website. You have full access to disable the notifications from the settings page in your profile. Your IP-address may be used to determine your location such as your city and country as this helps us serve you better. We do not sell, lease or distribute your personal information to any other company or organization unless it is permitted by you and/or it is required by the government agencies. 

What is a Cookie?

A cookie is a file stored within your browser and it is used to save your login information so that next time when you visit the website you don’t need to login again. There may also be some additional cookies stored by our advertising partners. 

Content

ASPForums.Net is a free platform for allowing users to ask questions and provide answers to those questions. You may choose to use it in your projects at your own risk and nor ASPForums.Net or its users are not responsible if it does not work as intended. 

Links to external websites

The posted Questions and Answers may contain links to external websites which ASPForums.Net cannot control and is not responsible for the privacy guidelines of such websites, thus as a precautionary measure please read their privacy policy. 

Contact

If you have any objections regarding the website content, its external links, users or your information privacy, please don’t hesitate to contact us.
